zoomin.tv 2016-05-12

# ZOOMIN.TV PRIVACY POLICY

ZOOMIN.TV PRIVACY POLICY
Last updated: 5 August 2014
We're always working to make our services even better. One of the ways we do that is by
analyzing information we collect and receive about users in order to figure out what they might
be interested in. This helps us develop more engaging content and provide more effective
advertising, which enables us to keep most of our services free.
This Privacy Policy describes how Zoom.in Group B.V. and all its subsidiaries and affiliates
(together: “Zoomin.TV”) handle the information we collect and receive about users. There are
three things you should keep in mind as you read it:
      1. The Privacy Policy applies to Zoomin.TV services that link to or refer to this Privacy Policy.
           These services include websites, mobile apps, other online services and anything else that
           links to or refers to this policy. To keep things simple, we refer to all these services as our
           "Services."
      2. The Privacy Policy is applicable no matter what computer or device you use to access our
           Services.
      3. We may provide additional information about the privacy practices of some of our
           Services. Although this Privacy Policy applies to all Zoomin.TV Services that refer or link to
           it, you should read the additional information, too. Some of this information is linked from
           various places in the Privacy Policy, and some is available through the individual Services
           that you use. We've done our best to keep this Privacy Policy short and simple, but if you
           have any questions about it, we hope you'll let us know.
Cookie Information and Opting Out
Harmless cookies that are designed to enhance your user experience of this website are stored
on your device. These consist of small data files relating to you and this website. Information
stored in cookies created by Zoomin.TV are not shared with any third party unless Zoomin.TV is
required to do so by law.
By continuing to browse this website you are consenting to the storage of first party cookies on
your device. Should you dissent to such storage of first party cookies, you can click here to
remove the cookies and discontinue browsing our website.
Information We Collect and Receive
We collect and receive information about users in a few different ways:
      a. Information you give us.
Postal address:    P.O. Box 2274 | 1000 CG Amsterdam                                    Phone: +31 20 320 99 75
Visiting address:  Hoogte Kadijk 143 F 25 | 1018 BH Amsterdam | The Netherlands         Fax: +31 20 427 19 91
www.zoomin.tv      Number 1 in online television

You can give us information directly. For example, when you post comments in response to a
story or video on any of our Services, we-and other users-receive that information.
When you otherwise contact us or provide us information directly.
      b. Information we collect or receive when you use our Services.
We also collect or receive information when you use our Services. We collect some of this
information using cookies, web beacons, and other technologies. Depending on how you access
and use our Services, we may receive:
      1. Log information. This is information we automatically collect and store when you use our
           Services or other companies' websites and apps in the Zoomin.TV Advertising Network. It
           may include information about your interactions with the websites, apps, and other
           services you use, the content you view, the search queries you submit, and information in
           cookies and similar technologies;
      2. Information about how you access those websites, apps, and other services, your browser
           or operating system, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, and the website you visited
           before visiting our Services.
      3. Device information. This is information we automatically collect and store about the
           device you use when you access our Services or the services in the Zoomin.TV Advertising
           Network. (Note that by "device," we mean anything you use to access our Services. Device
           information includes among others the type of device you're using (e.g., an iPhone),
           certain device identifiers which may be unique to your device and your Internet service
           provider.
      4. Location information. This information can include, for example, your device's GPS signal
           and information about nearby WiFi networks and cell towers. We get this information
           when you use location-enabled services.
      5. Information from third-party sources. We may receive additional information about you
           that is publicly or commercially available and combine that with the information we have
           collected or received about you in other ways. Also, we receive information about you
           when you choose to connect with social networking services while using our Services.
How We Use the Information We Collect and Receive
We use the information we collect and receive for the following general purposes:
Postal address:    P.O. Box 2274 | 1000 CG Amsterdam                                Phone: +31 20 320 99 75
Visiting address:  Hoogte Kadijk 143 F 25 | 1018 BH Amsterdam | The Netherlands     Fax: +31 20 427 19 91
www.zoomin.tv      Number 1 in online television

      1. To provide our Services. We use the information we collect and receive to provide you
           with the Services you use or request. For example, if you ask us to remember your login
           information for Zoomin.TV Services, we'll use information stored in cookies when you
           return to those websites.
      2. To improve our Services. We also use the information we collect and receive to provide
           content and advertising that people are likely to find relevant and engaging. For example,
           if we receive information from users that a Service isn't working properly, we may use
           that information to address any problem.
      3. To provide effective advertising. Many of our Services are supported by advertising, and
           some of our Services provide advertising on our websites and apps, and on third-party
           websites and apps. We use the information we collect and receive to make the advertising
           we provide more effective. Some of the ways we do this are: 1) showing you ads based on
           your online activities, such as the websites and applications you use, the content you
           view, and the searches you submit on those applications; 2) limiting the number of times
           you see the same ad; and 3) measuring the effectiveness of the ads we serve.
How We Share the Information We Collect and Receive
We don't rent or sell personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. But we
may share certain information we collect or receive with third parties to provide products and
services you have requested, when we have your consent, or as described in this Privacy Policy.
We may share information with:
      1. Affiliates. The information one Zoomin.TV affiliate receives can be shared among other
           Zoomin.TV affiliates.
      2. Business partners. We may share non-personally identifiable information with select
           business partners, who may use the information for a variety of purposes, including to
           provide you with relevant advertising.
      3. Other parties in response to legal process or when necessary to protect our Services. We
           may disclose your information-including the contents of your communications with other
           parties-to other parties, such as when we have a good faith belief that: a) it is necessary to
           respond to lawful governmental requests or legal process (for example, a court order,
           search warrant, or subpoena); b) the information is relevant to a crime that has been or is
           being committed; c) an emergency exists that poses a threat to your safety or the safety
           of another person; or d) it is necessary to protect the rights or property of Zoomin.TV.
      4. Other parties in connection with certain business transactions. In the event that the
           ownership of Zoomin.TV or an affiliate or their assets changes as a result of a merger,
           acquisition, sale of assets, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, your information may
Postal address:    P.O. Box 2274 | 1000 CG Amsterdam                                   Phone: +31 20 320 99 75
Visiting address:  Hoogte Kadijk 143 F 25 | 1018 BH Amsterdam | The Netherlands        Fax: +31 20 427 19 91
www.zoomin.tv     Number 1 in online television

           be transferred to another company. If we believe a transfer results in a material change in
           the use of the information we've collected or received about you, you will be given the
           opportunity to opt out of the transfer.
      5. Companies that provide services to Zoomin.TV.
      6. Companies that provide services to us or act on our behalf may have access to
           information about you. These companies are limited in their ability to use information
           they receive in the course of providing services to us.
Third Parties that Provide Content, Advertising Services, or Functionality on Our
Services
Some of the content, advertising, and functionality on our Services may be provided by third
parties that are not affiliated with us. Such third parties include:
      1. Advertising providers, which help us and our advertising customers provide ads that are
           tailored to users' interests and understand how users respond to those ads;
      2. Audience-measurement companies, which help us measure the overall usage of our
           Services and compare that usage to other online services; and
      3. Social networking services (like Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and Google ) that enable you
           to login to certain of our Services and to share things you find on our Services with your
           social network.
These and other third parties may collect or receive information about your use of our Services,
including through the use of cookies, web beacons and other technologies, and this information
may be collected over time and combined with information collected on different websites and
online services.
Note that some of these companies participate in industry-developed programs designed to
provide consumers with choices about whether to receive targeted ads. To learn more, please
visit the websites of the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance.
If you choose to connect with a social networking service, such as Facebook, we may share
information with that service, and that service may share information about you with us. We may
use the information for the reasons explained in this Privacy Policy, but the main reason we use it
is to make your experience on our Services more personal and social. For example, we might
show you what content is popular among your connections on the social networking service or
give you a glimpse of what your friends are saying about that content.
Postal address:    P.O. Box 2274 | 1000 CG Amsterdam                                 Phone: +31 20 320 99 75
Visiting address:  Hoogte Kadijk 143 F 25 | 1018 BH Amsterdam | The Netherlands      Fax: +31 20 427 19 91
www.zoomin.tv      Number 1 in online television

It's important to remember that we don't control the privacy practices of these (or any other)
third-party services. So we encourage you to read the privacy policies of the services before
connecting to them.
"Do Not Track" Signals
Some web browsers may transmit "do not track" signals to the websites and other online services
with which the browser communicates. There is no standard that governs what, if anything,
websites should do when they receive these signals. Zoomin.TV currently does not take action in
response to these signals. If and when a standard for responding is established, we may revisit its
policy on responding to these signals.
Our Commitment to Security
Although no one can guarantee the security of the information collected and received, we do
employ a number of safeguards intended to mitigate the risk of unauthorized access or disclosure
of this information. Examples of the types of safeguards we may provide (depending on the
circumstances) include:
      1. Storing the data you provide in controlled facilities;
      2. Using HTTPS encryption when you authenticate (i.e., log into one of our Services), which
           helps prevent unauthorized access to your login credentials;
      3. Limiting access to personal information to employees who need that access to perform
           their jobs; and
      4. Providing company-wide training on privacy and data security.
Children's Privacy
Our Services are intended for a general audience. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose
personal information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent. If you are
a parent who consents to the collection of personal information from your child, you agree that
your child may use all of our Services and that we may collect, use, and disclose your child's
personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy.
If you have questions concerning our information practices with respect to children, or if you
would like to review, have deleted, or stop the further collection of your child's personal
information, you may contact us:
By mail: Zoom.in BV, Hoogte Kadijk 143 F25, 1018 BH Amsterdam, the Netherlands
Postal address:    P.O. Box 2274 | 1000 CG Amsterdam                             Phone: +31 20 320 99 75
Visiting address:  Hoogte Kadijk 143 F 25 | 1018 BH Amsterdam | The Netherlands  Fax: +31 20 427 19 91
www.zoomin.tv      Number 1 in online television

By phone: +31 (0)20 320 9975
How to Contact Us
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or about Zoomin.TV's privacy practices
in general, please send us an email to info@zoomin.tv
Changes to This Privacy Policy and Additional Information
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy
periodically. If there are significant changes to Zoomin.TV's information practices, you will be
provided with appropriate online notice.
Postal address:   P.O. Box 2274 | 1000 CG Amsterdam                             Phone: +31 20 320 99 75
Visiting address: Hoogte Kadijk 143 F 25 | 1018 BH Amsterdam | The Netherlands  Fax: +31 20 427 19 91
www.zoomin.tv     Number 1 in online television
